A range friends if you have a car and
it shows the range on the display, I will
show you how it looks and
what is the actual range shown in it,
let's see
[music]
that this experience, get a petrol car in
kilometer, if you have
not subscribed to the channel then please
subscribe to my channel by subscribing, you can decide as per your wish whether
you want to buy it or not, I have a question that what is the
minimum
range of X1.1, how much range do you need, do
not cancel it, I will have under plus
range, even if it is more than 1051,
let's talk about this, welcome to
my channel Dr Rajesh Meena, Dr Girish, and so on, when
this launch event happened, people
started abusing the company that it was
said to be 191 but it is showing 135 on your screen
and especially then on the rival channel
Pradeep ji, on
Thursday, he drove it for some time, it could
not be done properly, people
started subscribing that the war has been cheated, so
friends when you drive a car, then the
petrol appointed in it is never correct  It happens that
whatever you use, there is always a shortage.
Similarly, if any company
tells more about mileage, there is a
notification that it does it, but
now if someone has been appointed here, then they start
abusing people, so it seems a little bit that you should have
thought a little bit about it,
subscribe. If Pradeep has not subscribed to his channel, then
subscribe. So how can you trust that screen, it is possible that he was going to do
all this properly. He was
his
friend and there are many things and it is a
very difficult task to tell something, that if
25 liters of petrol of Yuva Sangh is left, then 45
liters of petrol stops showing the range.
This happens in my life that when there is less petrol,
you cannot show the range in it. If you cannot make that much sense, then you will
show it too. The person
went on trusting him. If we get trapped somewhere, then the
company can say that you had
told so much range, you had told more, I could
not reach the petrol pump, I was
going on an important work and I incurred a loss of crores. So to
avoid all these things,
people come less and mileage is a little less.
Telling the stand, he is from the village, it is
70,
but many times you should
subscribe to the
same company, he had said but he had said
that your speed is coming high, you have done a
great job, till now all the
electric scooters in the market, the
maximum speed was about nine
kilometers, that my knowledge through that
he had said that the young man had said, so
subscription is a different thing for scooters,
but whatever happens,
use it like subscription, I
want kilometer channel subscription, according to me it is
continuously
appointed, so if things are
tested as they are, it is better, you will know
2 inches in it, whereas if we talk about
many people, we gave so much money,
we wanted so much, do
not forget to
subscribe, from 30-40 thousand, scooters
are available in the market,
60 are available as per the budget,
but you will get performance as per the budget
and they are saying that they had promised that they will
subscribe, it
seems wrong, if any company should
not give subscription despite low subscription, let's
break the promise, then this is  A company
subscribe button click practical test
someone has done then
subscribe here I will send it to you
and now school
subscribe to
[music]
Ajay